http://www.burli.com/privacy

Benefits
Why Burli?
Benefits
Why Burli?
Contact Us
We have provided this Privacy Policy to let you know how Burli collects, uses and manages information on this web site.
What Information We Collect
Burli collects comparatively little data about visitors to this website. We may log visitors IP address and which pages are accessed by that IP address. We use this information for our own statistics, and to improve the usefulness of the website. We do not share this information with other companies except those directly involved with hosting or maintaining this website. We make no attempt to determine personal information, including your e-mail address, except where you explicitly volunteer the information to us on a form or in an e-mail.
Support Logins and Passwords
Registered support customer can access certain portions of the Burli website by entering a specific username and password. In these sections of the website, we do log specific users’ identities, but we collect this information to provide visitors with personalised support services. We do not share this information with any other company or organisation except those directly involved in hosting and maintaining the website.
Personal Information
In some places on the website, we may ask you to provide some personal information by filling out and submitting an online form. These forms are completely optional. However please understand that in some cases some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and if you do not provide the mandatory data, you will not be able to engage in the activity associated with it.
When you submit personal information to Burli through this site, please understand that the information may be transferred unencrypted across several national boundaries. Burli will make reasonable efforts to maintain the security of your personal information and will not share or sell the information.We never ask for or collect personal financial information, including credit card numbers or banking information, anywhere on our website.
Use of Cookies
Like many other websites, Burli.com may use a standard technology called a “cookie” to store some information on your local computer while you use the site and between sessions. The cookies on this site do not collect any personal information about you or your computer. If you are just browsing this website, our cookies identify only your browser. It is possible to set your browser to inform you when a cookie is being placed — this way, you have the opportunity to decide whether to accept the cookie.
External Links
From time to time, the Burli website provides links to other websites. While we believe these links to be useful and to point to legitimate and reputable websites, we have no control over those websites nor over their privacy policies. Burli’s privacy policy does not extend to any of these external links. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of each website you access before you use it.
Technical Support Call +1-604-684-3140
Email Burli Support
Visit the Support Site
Get the Remote Support Tool
What’s New
Forbes names Burli an 'Innovator to Watch' in media
SQL Server 2008 reaches End-of-Life
QGoLive integration added to Burli Newsroom and NE
We ask a newscaster "Why Burli?"
We talk to a University professor about his use of Burli in the classroom
Learn about Burli's Audio Logger
Learn about Burli's Quick Record
Learn about the Burli Multi Track Editor
Sign Up for Our Newsletter Get a quick dose of Burli News every few months.
Feeling Social?
Burli News Burli Adds Support for QGoLive
Burli and QGoLive have added amazing integration hooks to make gathering the news even easier.
More News…
Our Customers Say “Absolutely superb.  Fantastic.  One of, if not the best vendors we deal with!”.
Why Burli?
